Love Object is a drama, horror, romance film directed by Robert Parigi.
The twisted tale of Kenneth, socially insecure technical writer who forms an obsessive relationship
with "Nikki", an anatomically accurate silicone sex doll he orders over the Internet.
Kenneth Winslow, played by Desmond Harrington.
Lisa Bellmer, played by Melissa Sagemiller.
Radley, played by Udo Kier.
Novak, played by Rip Torn.
Jason, played by John Cassini.
Dotson (as Brad Henke), played by Brad William Henke.
Love Object is a 2003 American horror film
written and directed by Robert Parigi.
Kenneth (played by Desmond Harrington) is an efficient but socially awkward technical writer who
develops an obsessive relationship with Nikki, a realistic sex doll he purchases.
The film explores themes of mannequin, sex shop, obsession, detective, office.
The tone is dark and intense and emotional.